[exhales]
Think you'll be okay
waiting here by yourself?
Yeah. Whatever.
Uh, sir,
if you'd like to smoke,
you need to be another
20 feet from the door.
So roll me further, bitch.
[ambulance siren in distance]
What's coming?
Male Caucasian.
Early 40s.
Multiple gunshot wounds.
BP is 70. 7-0 over palp.
Pulse 140-- 1-4-0.
Weak and thready
at the brachial.
No breath sounds
on the right side,
and the belly is rigid.
Patient appears pale
and diaphoretic.
How many entry wounds?
We found four-- shoulder and
hip, through and through.
Right lung
and lower left quadrant,
no visible exit wounds.
Let's give him
2 grams of oxygen.
What's his hemoglobin?
7.3.
I need two
large-bore IVs,
6 units O-neg,
type and cross
for 6 more units,
Chest X-ray and KUB.
Notify the O.R.
we are on the way.
[door buzzes]
O.R. One is clear.
Let's put him in there.
[door closes]
[exhales]
♪ [rock in distance]
Yo, Jesse, sorry I'm late, man.
Damn, brother, look at you.
That's messed up.
How are you feeling?
You okay?
Actually...
I'm great.
[Gale] I don't understand.
I thought things were
going pretty well.
I--
I thought we were
kind of simpatico,
you know?
We were becoming a real team.
Uh, not-- not so much, no.
Is this about the temperature
setting the other day?
Because I can assure you
that will not happen--
No, it's bigger
than that, Gale.
It's-- It's-- It's
much more than that.
Could you elaborate?
Well, uh, yes,
of course I could,
but I don't think either of us
would necessarily benefit
from a prolonged...
Uh, yeah, so...
Yeah.
I set up the entire lab.
You said you liked
the configuration.
And I do.
For the most part.
Look, you're a fine
chemist, really,
with a promising future.
It's just that--
that I--
that-- that we just have
different...
Rhythms, Gale.
It's-- It's--
It's as if I'm classical
but you are-- are more...
Jazz.
Yes.
And God knows there is
nothing wrong with jazz.
It's simply
that I require--
Classical.
Exactly.
[door opens]
Oh, shit.
Man, this is the bomb.
What's up, partner?
[Jesse] Ohh.
I can't believe this.
This is my replacement?
[Jesse] Oh, Jesus.
Hi. Gale. Nice to meet you.
What's up?
Damn, we should have
ditched that RV months ago.
It's all, like,
shining up in here.
Oh!
[Jesse chuckles]
I'm sorry. I must be
missing something.
I don't mean--
I don't mean to be--
[Jesse]
Oh! Oh!
This-- [Jesse] No!
...makes no sense.
[Jesse laughing]
So...
I guess this is--
[Jesse]
Oh, dear mother of God.
This is for the best.
200 pounds a week.
Got it?
Uh-huh.
[Jesse]
Oh, man! Oh!
Mr. White!
[door opens, closes]
Wow.
[laughing]
Okay. There's a lot
to show you.
Some new techniques to learn.
What, now?
Yes, now.
We've only got a couple days
before our next batch is due,
and I need to get you
up to speed.
Right on.
I'm just saying--
How's the cell service
down here?
It's nonexistent.
We're shielded.
There's a hard line
for emergencies. Come on.
So you haven't talked
to anybody today
other than, you know,
Captain Nerd there.
Why?
Your brother-in-law.
What about him?
So what's the story?
Upon arrival, he was unresponsive.
Take a look. You getting some
exposure on those wounds?
...blood pressure of 80.
2 units of normal saline.
We've got a bivalve mass.
He's got breath sounds
bilaterally.
This femur feels
like a wet bag of gravel.
The other one's
not much better.
Let's get those boots off.
See if you get a pulse.
You get a blood pressure
cup or an ABI?
Where's that blood?
Sir, can I help you?
Uh, yeah, I--
It's all right.
He's family.
Thank you.
Marie.
I'm so sorry.
Hey.
I don't know what to say.
How is he?
I don't know. They won't
really tell us anything.
He's still in surgery.
They shot him four times.
Oh, Christ.
Where's Holly?
I got a sitter.
Hey. How are you, huh?
Fine.
Yeah?
Sure?
I-- I'm fine. I just need
some fresh air.
Okay.
Here.
Let me get the door.
I got it. I'm fine.
Walt.
Hmm?
Walt, this is ASAC Merkert.
Hank's
brother-in-law Walt.
Hello.
I'm very sorry.
Thank you. Uh--
Can you tell us anything
or any details?
Right now, all we know
is two men ambushed Hank.
They didn't have any I.D.
on them.
Probably Mexican nationals.
Their tattoos
indicated an affiliation
with the drug cartel.
Why did they attack Hank?
We're not sure yet.
It could be in relation
to an investigation
that Hank was working,
or it could be a message
to the DEA in general.
They had an ax.
The cartels tend
to be dramatic.
Oh, Jesus.
Where are they?
I mean, did they--
Hank got both of them.
He killed one outright,
and the other one's upstairs
in critical condition.
Your brother-in-law's
one tough son of a bitch
to take them both out,
considering he didn't
even have his gun.
He didn't have his gun?
Why didn't Hank have his gun?
Marie, the assault charge.
I had to suspend Hank
pending the investigation.
That means I had to
take away his weapon.
[muttering]
It's standard procedure.
No one--
Okay, All right. Listen.
If you would have all
listened to him
right from the start,
and let him arrest
that little degenerate,
he wouldn't have had to take
things into his own hands,
and he would have had a gun
and defended himself.
Marie,
let's just--
No. Just--
It's their fault.
He didn't have a gun.
Honey, this isn't helping you.
You.
What kind of partner are you?
You were supposed
to back him up,
and where were you?
Where were you?
Texas.
And you.
You're supposed to
protect your agents
instead of taking their guns,
not supporting them,
not backing them up--
Marie. Marie.
...when they--
Honey, let's just go
and sit down, okay?
I'm not doing anything
until these two get
the hell out of here.
I mean it.
Sorry--
Go.
You are not welcome here.
The DEA is not welcome here.
Honey.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go sit down.
It's not just them.
It's you, Walt.
This Pinkman that Hank
was looking for--
Hank would have never
even heard his name
if you hadn't bought
marijuana from him.
Marie--
Do you ever think
about that, Walt?
Do you?
Do you ever think
about everything
that you have put him through?
[Skyler] Marie, stop.
You're upset,
and you're looking
for someone to blame,
and it's understandable,
but don't blame Walt.
It's not his fault.
I'm sorry.
Sweetheart. No.
No. No. Don't--
[sobbing]
It's okay.
It's Hank--
It's all right.
Shh.
[sobbing]
All right, you're done.
Okay, next.
Hello!
[imitating echo] Hello,
hello, hello, hello, hello.
Yeah.
Wow.
[grunt]
Yo, yo, yo!
Jesse Pinkman in the house!
Oh, my dear God.
[laughs]
Wow.
[beep]
Walter White to the nearest
courtesy phone.
Walter White, please
pick up a courtesy phone.
[Jesse] Yo.
We working sometime this year?
What the hell
are you thinking?
Why are you calling me here?
I tried your cell, and it
went straight to voice mail.
How else am I supposed
to get hold of you?
You aren't.
Look, man,
it's been a whole day.
How long is this
grieving process?
Just put a clock on it for me.
All's I'm saying is
we have a schedule, right?
My family comes
before your schedule.
Dude, it's not
my schedule.
We have responsibilities here.
I'll get there
when I get there.
You know what? Whatever.
I'll just cook on my own.
You will do no such thing.
Why not?
Well, uh, for starters,
you aren't
the least bit familiar
with any of the equipment.
There's got to be some
sort of manual, right?
And I can read.
Jesse, touch nothing.
Yo, stop treating me
I'm like your assistant.
I'm not your bitch
to order around.
We're partners.
Remember?
I need you to sit patiently
and wait, and I will be there
as soon as I can.
Thank you very much
for your kind words.
We-- We really do
appreciate that.
What, is your wife there?
Uh, yes. Yes, she is,
and she would be happy to know
that you asked about her.
And please do keep us
in your thoughts.
Hey, tell your douche-bag
brother-in-law
to head towards the light.
So I'm thinking, um,
maybe we should go get
everybody some breakfast.
Yeah. That sounds good.
Do you know who that was?
You know, these eggs
are really not too bad.
Look at that.
Look at what?
At what? This. These spots.
This fork is absolutely filthy.
Tell me you see this.
You've got good eyes.
Look at that.
Marie, those
are just water spots.
Fork is fine.
Those are not water spots.
That's dirt.
This silverware's
obviously not been cleaned.
It's covered in germs
from someone else's mouth.
God knows what.
Seriously, Aunt Marie,
it's water spots.
Ours at home aren't any better.
Yours at home are irrelevant.
We're in a hospital.
They need to be held
to a higher standard.
They have a responsibility.
Well, I'm not actually sure
if the cafeteria
necessarily qualifies
as being part of a hospital.
It's in the same building.
It's all under the same roof.
Do you think that sick
people aren't eating
with this bacteria-infected
silverware?
My Gpd, how are you supposed
to survive this death trap?
[Skyler] Marie.
I survived.
I had my lumpectomy
at this hospital.
Remember that?
Remember how scared
we all were?
Whoo.
I didn't want to act like it,
but I was terrified.
All that week,
all I could think of
was how they were actually
going to cut me open
and take out a part of me
that was with me
my entire life.
I couldn't get that image
out of my head.
I think the scariest part
was when...
They took me into pre-op,
lying there,
waiting for them
to anesthetize you,
knowing that...
You may never wake up again.
[chuckles] Actually,
what I really remember
about that day
is driving to the hospital.
Skyler, you remember me
wanting to drive that day?
Yeah.
Anyway, there we are.
We're driving up Central,
and we hit every green light--
I mean, every single light
that we hit--
sheew-- green.
[chuckling]
When does that happen?
Just like bang, bang,
green the entire way.
And the whole time,
all I could think about
was "Why today? Why?
"Why can't I just spend
a few extra minutes
in the car with my family?"
I never wanted to be stuck
in traffic so bad in my life.
At least I was with my family.
I had that.
Anyway, I survived this place.
And I'm not half the man
your husband is.
[phone buzzes]
Yes?
[Man speaking Spanish]
I was going to ask you
the same question.
I heard they they
attacked a DEA agent.
Why would they do that?
I didn't order this,
and my men would never
do this on their own.
Someone gave the go-ahead.
Are you
accusing me?
I'm just saying they
wouldn't act on their own.
I am not in the habit
of picking my own pocket.
I assume
that the next shipment
will be delayed.
Any thoughts on when
it might arrive?
A week, a month.
There's too much
focus on the border.
We lay low for the time being.
We lay low,
and then we get the real story
from my man who survived.
Your man is in custody.
He's innocent
until proven guilty.
Correct?
I'll get him the best lawyer,
and then
we'll learn the truth.
Well, keep me apprised.
Any time you've got that close
proximity to the spine,
there's always going
to be cause for concern,
but, as I say,
it's really too soon to tell.
He's out of surgery,
at least, which is--
Out of surgery,
on his way to revery.
All right.
Where's that?
Unfortunately,
you can't see him just yet.
We're gonna have to wait
for him to stabilize.
How long will that take?
I can't really say.
Could be hours,
but we'll let you know just
as soon as you could see him.
Thank you.
Um, maybe we should get
you home for a couple hours?
Get some rest?
I'm not going anywhere.
Me, neither.
Well, is anyone else dying
to brush their teeth,
or is it just me?
What if I ran over to the house
and picked up a few things?
Marie? I could
swing by your place.
That would be great.
Thanks, Walt.
Okay.
[Woman on P.A.]
Dr. Bender?
Dr. Bender.
Walt. Walt.
We just heard he came through?
Yeah, well, it's, uh,
you know, guardedly good news.
Thank God.
I'll take it. Yeah.
Hey, guys, this is
Hank's brother-in-law, Walt.
Hi.
Hello.
We were just swapping
Hank stories.
Oh, well, that could--
that could go on all day.
God knows,
there's a million of them.
Meanwhile...
Miserable piece of shit.
Guy who shot him,
the one that's left,
he's up there,
got the painkillers going on,
resting comfortably.
Your tax dollars at work.
You ought to see what
Hank did to that bastard.
Want to see?
Come on, let me show you.
We can do this?
You comfortable,
you piece of shit?
[monitor beeping]
[beeping increases]
[monitor flatlines]
[glass crashes]
[monitor alarm beeping]
You got him?
Yeah.
[Man] Come on.
Easy, easy.
[wheels clattering]
[Jesse grunts]
Whoa!
[wheels clattering]
Oh! Oh!
♪ [rap]
[air vent whirring]
Come on.
Oh.
No.
[grunts]
Ho!
[crashing] Ouch.
♪ [continues]
♪ Fallacies ♪
♪ One for you and two for-- ♪
[groans]
[air hisses]
[air hissing]
Yeah!
[door slams]
Finally. About damn time.
♪ [ends]
[hissing stops]
Why isn't there
anything cooking?
[beep]
Walter White to the nearest
courtesy phone.
Operator.
This is Walter White.
I'll connect you.
[beep]
[Jesse] Yo, we got
problems, big ones.
Reverend,
so nice of you to call...
Again.
Turn your phone on already.
You know, I will
definitely look into that.
I'll tell you what. Why don't I just
call you right back on my cell phone.
Okay?
I told you to wait.
I don't know how many
more ways I could say it.
Yeah, damn, I was waiting,
and then that creepy,
quiet guy showed up.
Gus came by?
Not him, man.
Apparently I'm not worthy
of meeting him.
It was the other one, the one
that I'm qualified to speak to.
Then he started asking
questions, too,
like why
I haven't cooked anything.
We have a quota.
It's due tomorrow.
Do you seriously not care,
or what?
Because that guy, he's got,
like, the dead eyes.
Let me ask you something.
Do you remember when we were
out in the desert with Tuco?
Oh, you mean when he put
a machinegun to my head?
Yeah, I think that does ring
a tiny bell. Why?
No. He kept-- He kept saying
that-- that someone
was coming up
from Mexico to get us.
Do you remember?
Now, who was that?
What the hell has
this even got to do with--
Look, I don't know.
It was, um--
uh...
His cousins.
Right, Jesse?
It was his cousins.
Yeah, cousins.
Whatever, man. Why?
Any news?
[Marie] No change.
Okay. Well, I--
I didn't know whose
toothbrushes were whose, so I--
I just stopped
by the drugstore.
Thank God
for travel sizes, right?
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, I think I'm going
to go wash my face.
I'm going crazy.
Do you want to come?
Yeah.
I got candy bars.
Oh, um--
Is this what
you were asking for?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, I--
I skimmed through it.
Looks interesting.
Yeah.
Uncle Hank gave it to me.
What's it about?
Pablo Escobar,
this big drug guy in the '80s.
Yeah. Yeah, I remember
seeing him on the news.
Well, it's more about
the guys who investigated him
and tried to bring him down.
Some of them were DEA,
you know?
Uncle Hank said that they
were worth learning about,
that everybody knows
who Pablo Escobar is,
but nobody knows about the guys
that brought him down.
I guess I never thought
about it.
[chuckles]
He said that good guys
never get ink
like the bad guys do.
[chuckles]
So he gave it to me.
Figured I'd read it.
[cell phone ringing]
Uh, I-- I need to--
I'll be right back, okay?
No, I assure you.
We are hard at work.
Absolutely.
[Gus] So I can expect delivery
by tomorrow as scheduled.
Well, uh--
No. Unfortunately--
Unfortunately,
we're not going to be able
to keep our schedule this week.
But not for lack of trying.
Is there something
I should know?
Well, to be completely
honest with you...
Gale really screwed us up.
I mean, not on purpose,
of course,
but he just--
he set us way back,
and we've been playing
catch-up ever since.
And I've had to be out
running errands
and trying to keep us
on target.
Some of the equipment
wasn't calibrated
correctly and--
Well, it's just all
very technical and boring,
but rest assured that--
that we will
do whatever it takes.
It has my total attention.
We'll cook through
the weekend if necessary.
We will have 400 pounds
for you by next week.
I have your word on that?
You do.
You have my word on that.
Thank you for the update.
Any news?
Nah, I'm just-- just wandering.
How's everybody doing?
Well, as well
as can be expected.
It's this not knowing
that's the hardest part,
I think.
Anything new on these guys?
Who they are?
What they wanted?
No, nothing yet,
but we'll get it.
Steve...
Do you think
there could maybe be others?
Buddy, nobody's getting
to Hank.
That was their one shot,
and they blew it.
So, no.
No way.
Jesus.
I'd love to walk in there
and shoot that bastard
right in the head.
Me, too.
[cell phone rings]
Yeah.
Oh, yeah?
Great. We'll be right down.
Food's here.
Hey, you like Pollos Hermanos?
Uh, on occasion, yeah.
Owner's a big booster
for the DEA.
He heard what happened.
He's going to feed every cop in the building.
That's-- That's wonderful.
Yeah, and apparently he's
bringing it by personally.
[elevator bell dings]
[Marie] I don't even
know what to say.
[Skyler]
That's an incredible--
Good, huh?
Delicious.
[Marie] That's so generous of you.
Thank you very much.
[Skyler] Yes, thank you.
Guys, did you hear that?
Mr. Fring is offering
a $10,000 reward
on any information
about the case.
Well, that's--
that's wonderful.
Wow. Thank you, Mr. Fring.
You're very welcome.
Men like your husband
are the thin blue line
between us and these animals.
I only wish I could do more.
Well, we do appreciate
your support.
This reward could turn
the tide here.
It'll really help.
Again, I can't express
how sorry I am.
As it happens,
I actually met Agent Schrader.
[Marie] Really?
Our fun run,
a couple months ago.
Mr. Fring
was one of our sponsors.
I talked for a few minutes
with your husband.
As a matter of fact,
Mr. White, your name came up.
Really? Huh.
Yeah, there happened to be
a collection jar out for you,
and we spoke briefly
about your health concerns.
I hope that there's been
good news.
Uh, yeah, things
have improved, yes.
That's wonderful to hear.
It was clear to me
how deeply he cares for you.
Well, I've taken up
enough of your time.
Um... thank you
again very much.
It was a great pleasure
to meet you.
Thank you.
[Walter, Jr.] Yes, thank you.
Let me walk you out.
Oh-- Oh, no, it's not necessary.
You know,
I didn't say thank you.
I'll walk him out.
I'll be right back.
Hi. How are you?
Good to see you.
Enjoying the chicken?
Good. Good-- Hey.
Oh, you're very welcome.
My pleasure.
My pleasure, yeah.
Excuse me.
Thank you. Thank you.
It's good chicken, huh?
Yeah.
Good.
Mr. Fring.
May I--
Mr. White.
I just wanted
to thank you again.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
Uh, may I--
may I speak with you?
Just a moment?
You knew.
You knew my brother-in-law
was with the DEA.
I investigate everyone
with whom I do business.
What careful man wouldn't?
He is not a problem for us,
for our business.
Your being here is--
Is this some sort of message?
I'm supporting my community.
I hide in plain sight,
same as you.
Are we done?
No-- No, listen, I--
This attack
on my brother-in-law--
I don't--
I don't understand it.
I don't know what it means.
Please, if you have
some knowledge
that you could share with me.
I fear for my family.
I'm sure they'll be fine.
I am told the assassin
that survived
is gravely injured.
It's doubtful he'll live.
Now thank me and shake my hand.
Uh-- thank you.
Thank you again.
You're quite welcome,
Mr. White.
What's going on?
What's happening?
[Woman]
Starting chest compressions.
One, two, three, four.
[monitor flatlines]
[alarm beeping]
One, two, three--
[Man] Defib?
No reason.
Patient is--
Continuing chest compressions.
One, two, three, four.
Give me a liter of saline wide open.
I can't get a pulse back.
One, two, three, four.
[Man] Still nothing.
One, two, three--
All right.
Stopping compressions.
Time.
8:43.
Time of death. 20:43.
[steadbeep]
Burn in hell,
you piece of shit.
[sizzling]
[cell phone vibrating]
Yes? Juan?
[Bolsa]
I assume you heard the news.
Your man died.
I heard.
It's unfortunate.
Yeah, "unfortunate,"
and meanwhile I have Federales
surrounding my house.
You know what I think, Gustavo?
I think you're behind all this.
Why would I do this?
How would it serve me?
That's the part I'm trying
to figure out.
Go off on your own, maybe.
Would you actually think
that would work?
Juan, you sound like
you're under a lot of stress.
Maybe you should call me back
when you're seeing things
more clearly.
I see things clear enough.
One DEA gets shot.
All of Washington starts barking.
The D.F. suddenly
has to put on a big show,
and I wind up with Federales
in my rose bushes.
But just for a while.
Appearances, politics.
Are you still there,
Gustavo?
Yes, I'm here.
I'll weather this.
I always do.
My brother's a police chief.
I got connections.
They'll get me through.
And when I get proof
and the others find out
what you've done,
maybe we come pay you a visit.
Maybe we c--
[glass pops, shatters]
[speaks Spanish]
[Men shouting]
[shouts in Spanish]
[gunfire]
[speaks Spanish]
[glass shatters]
[gunfire]
Skyler. Skyler.
Marie. Marie.
Oh, how is he?
Tell me something good.
I think he's stable enough now
for you to go see him briefly.
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
it's immediately family only.
We're all family.
I understand,
but we have a certain protocol
here that we need--
We're all family.
[monitor beeping]
[respirator hissing]
SubtitleSync (http://www.subtitlesync.com.ar)
www.tvsubtitles.net